Hello, thank you, everybody, for coming.
I'm Amanda Seals.
I brought you all here to make a major announcement.
Are you going back to the real?
No, it got canceled.
What's he talking about?
You pregnant, too?
What?
That is rude.
But everybody is pregnant, right?
That's crazy.
So who's the father?
Derek.
Derek Dubois.
That's the father.
You happy?
Is that really your head?
Are you biracial?
No, I'm not biracial.
Not that there's anything wrong with that.
It's just I'm not.
Clearly, there's massive up in here,
but my parents are both black, black.
You starting a podcast?
I've had a podcast for five years.
Small doses.
Check it out.
You?
Do you still hate black men?
I have never.
Y'all.
I have never hated black men.
I just am not a fan of bitch-ass niggas.
Have you changed your stance on passports?
Wow.
Y'all bringing up.
Oh, shit.
No, I still think if you have money for Jordans and tracksuits
and you are not in possession of a passport,
you're losing.
Especially if you live in Florida.
Get out of there.
Is your mother white?
You're joking, right?
Okay.
Reclaiming my time.
I was wanting to do that.
I came here to tell y'all this.
Fourscore and seven pandemic years ago,
we the people, in order to have a dream,
used to read Word Up magazine.
Girl, what are you trying to say?
Okay, I was trying to be presidential.
Really what I'm trying to say is,
I came here today to announce that after four years,
I've decided to drop a political comedy documentary.
Oh, I don't know.
Oh, that's it?
Yes, that's it.
What you doing?
You ain't here in the middle of the day.
You don't get a job.
Look out for In Amanda We Trust coming soon.
Is it going to be on HBO?
Yeah.
No, it is not going to be on HBO.
They said they don't have room.
So I did it myself,
because I didn't want to wait for nobody.
You feel me?
Yes, that insecure money is being put to good use.
Black women doing things.
So y'all going to have my back, right?
Because I got a mortgage.
You're going to help me seals the deal.
Ha-ha!
And I'm going to be hitting the campaign trail
to remind y'all I got these jokes.
So look out for when I'm at a spot near you.
All right, go to In AmandaWeTrust.com.
Ba-dum-bum!
Everybody know light-skinned folks ain't funny.
Can you just watch the trailer, please?
For deception and power rules,
one brave woman answers the call of the people.
I think I'm going to run for office.
And ventures to the nation's capital
to bring a trusted voice to the halls of democracy.
I mean, if I ran,
do you think you would vote for me?
It depends.
Oh!
I came through because I wanted to get some insight
from some folks who are already on the inside.
And, uh...
Oh, you Afro's needed here.
No one is going to believe me in this.
You know what?
You never told me,
what are you running for?
The question really is,
what are we running to?
I'm running to the people.
Oh!
Hey!
How well do you think you know government?
I went to school.
I can answer a couple questions.
How are you fighting the colonization?
Are you doing martial arts?
If I were in any office,
from alderman to state senator to Republican...
What Satan just flew into my mouth?
The Santas came in here, right?
That's what happened.
I'll act that.
In Amanda We Trust,
an unapologetically political comedy doc
from Amanda Seals,
coming soon to the internet.
Hear that motorcade?
That's Kamala going home.
That could be me.
In AmandaWeTrust.com.